<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

<VME_FleshcraftedArm.label>fleshcrafted arm</VME_FleshcraftedArm.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedArm.description>A biological human arm, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedArm.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedHand.label>fleshcrafted hand</VME_FleshcraftedHand.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedHand.description>A biological human hand, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedHand.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedFinger.label>fleshcrafted finger</VME_FleshcraftedFinger.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedFinger.description>A biological human finger, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedFinger.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedToe.label>fleshcrafted toe</VME_FleshcraftedToe.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedToe.description>A biological human toe, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedToe.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedLeg.label>fleshcrafted leg</VME_FleshcraftedLeg.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedLeg.description>A biological human leg, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedLeg.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedHeart.label>fleshcrafted heart</VME_FleshcraftedHeart.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedHeart.description>A biological human heart, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedHeart.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedLung.label>fleshcrafted lung</VME_FleshcraftedLung.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedLung.description>A biological human lung, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedLung.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedKidney.label>fleshcrafted kidney</VME_FleshcraftedKidney.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedKidney.description>A biological human kidney, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedKidney.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedLiver.label>fleshcrafted liver</VME_FleshcraftedLiver.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedLiver.description>A biological human liver, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedLiver.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedEye.label>fleshcrafted eye</VME_FleshcraftedEye.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedEye.description>A biological human eye, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedEye.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedEar.label>fleshcrafted ear</VME_FleshcraftedEar.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedEar.description>A biological human ear, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedEar.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedNose.label>fleshcrafted nose</VME_FleshcraftedNose.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedNose.description>A biological human nose, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedNose.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedJaw.label>fleshcrafted jaw</VME_FleshcraftedJaw.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedJaw.description>A biological human jaw, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedJaw.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedStomach.label>fleshcrafted stomach</VME_FleshcraftedStomach.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedStomach.description>A biological human stomach, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedStomach.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedTongue.label>fleshcrafted tongue</VME_FleshcraftedTongue.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedTongue.description>A biological human tongue, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedTongue.description>

<VME_FleshcraftedSpine.label>fleshcrafted spine</VME_FleshcraftedSpine.label>
<VME_FleshcraftedSpine.description>A biological human spine, fleshcrafted from a corpse. This can be safely installed in colonists following a Fleshcrafting ideoligion, but will cause infections due to organ rejection in others.</VME_FleshcraftedSpine.description>


</LanguageData>