<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

		<!-- +++++ Buildings_Ancient_Indoors +++++ -->
<VME_AncientSystemRack.label>ancient system rack</VME_AncientSystemRack.label>
<VME_AncientSystemRack.description>An ancient rack unit packed with unidentifiable devices. Valuable parts are missing, and everything else is degraded to uselessness.</VME_AncientSystemRack.description>

<VME_AncientEquipmentBlocks.label>ancient equipment blocks</VME_AncientEquipmentBlocks.label>
<VME_AncientEquipmentBlocks.description>A collection of ancient equipment blocks of unknown function. Valuable parts are missing, and everything else is degraded to uselessness.</VME_AncientEquipmentBlocks.description>

<VME_AncientMachine.label>ancient machine</VME_AncientMachine.label>
<VME_AncientMachine.description>A large ancient machine case filled with unknown machinery. Valuable parts are missing, and everything else is degraded to uselessness.</VME_AncientMachine.description>

<VME_AncientStorageCylinder.label>ancient storage cylinder</VME_AncientStorageCylinder.label>
<VME_AncientStorageCylinder.description>An ancient device that looks like it once stored some kind of fluid. Valuable parts are missing, and everything else is degraded to uselessness.</VME_AncientStorageCylinder.description>

<VME_AncientLamp.label>ancient lamp</VME_AncientLamp.label>
<VME_AncientLamp.description>An ancient self-powered lamp. Its internal power supply is badly depleted, but it still emits a weak glow.</VME_AncientLamp.description>

<VME_AncientBed.label>ancient bed</VME_AncientBed.label>
<VME_AncientBed.description>An old, rotted mattress on a rusty frame. Though uncomfortable, it can still be used, but its too dilapidated to restore.</VME_AncientBed.description>

<VME_AncientDisplayBank.label>ancient display bank</VME_AncientDisplayBank.label>
<VME_AncientDisplayBank.description>An ancient computer interface. Valuable parts are missing, and everything else is degraded to uselessness.</VME_AncientDisplayBank.description>

<VME_AncientLockerBank.label>ancient locker bank</VME_AncientLockerBank.label>
<VME_AncientLockerBank.description>An ancient, rusted bank of lockers. All of the lockers have been forced open with nothing valuable left behind.</VME_AncientLockerBank.description>

<VME_AncientCrate.label>ancient crate</VME_AncientCrate.label>
<VME_AncientCrate.description>An ancient, broken crate. Any valuables it once contained have degraded to uselessness.</VME_AncientCrate.description>

<VME_AncientMilitaryCrate.label>ancient military crate</VME_AncientMilitaryCrate.label>
<VME_AncientMilitaryCrate.description>An ancient, military-looking crate. It was broken long ago and any valuables it once contained were looted.</VME_AncientMilitaryCrate.description>

<VME_AncientSpacerCrate.label>ancient spacer crate</VME_AncientSpacerCrate.label>
<VME_AncientSpacerCrate.description>An ancient, broken crate. Any valuables it once contained were taken long ago.</VME_AncientSpacerCrate.description>

<VME_AncientBarrel.label>ancient barrel</VME_AncientBarrel.label>
<VME_AncientBarrel.description>An ancient, broken barrel that looks like it once contained waste of some sort. The only thing it contains now is a smear of dried sludge.</VME_AncientBarrel.description>

<VME_AncientGenerator.label>ancient generator</VME_AncientGenerator.label>
<VME_AncientGenerator.description>An ancient electrical generator. Its usable parts were smashed or looted long ago, and the rest has rusted into uselessness.</VME_AncientGenerator.description>

<VME_AncientOperatingTable.label>ancient operating table</VME_AncientOperatingTable.label>
<VME_AncientOperatingTable.description>A table once used for surgical operations. It has long since deteriorated into uselessness.</VME_AncientOperatingTable.description>

		<!-- +++++ Buildings_Ancient_Outdoors +++++ -->
<VME_AncientShoppingCart.label>ancient shopping cart</VME_AncientShoppingCart.label>
<VME_AncientShoppingCart.description>An ancient, rusted shopping cart. How exactly it got here is a mystery, but the story is long and probably quite sad.</VME_AncientShoppingCart.description>

<VME_AncientPostbox.label>ancient postbox</VME_AncientPostbox.label>
<VME_AncientPostbox.description>An ancient postbox, smashed and deteriorated to uselessness. It seems to have been moved here long ago for some unknown reason.</VME_AncientPostbox.description>

<VME_AncientVendingMachine.label>ancient vending machine</VME_AncientVendingMachine.label>
<VME_AncientVendingMachine.description>An ancient vending machine. It was smashed ages ago and generations of looters have taken every conceivably useful part. How it ended up here is a mystery.</VME_AncientVendingMachine.description>

<VME_AncientAirConditioner.label>ancient air conditioner</VME_AncientAirConditioner.label>
<VME_AncientAirConditioner.description>An ancient air conditioning machine. Its internals were smashed long ago and what wasnt looted has rusted away in the time since.</VME_AncientAirConditioner.description>

<VME_AncientKitchenSink.label>ancient kitchen sink</VME_AncientKitchenSink.label>
<VME_AncientKitchenSink.description>An ancient kitchen sink made of some non-metallic fiber-sheet material. It is badly deteriorated and theres no way to salvage anything from it.\n\nHow it got here must be a long story.</VME_AncientKitchenSink.description>

<VME_AncientStove.label>ancient stove</VME_AncientStove.label>
<VME_AncientStove.description>An ancient stove. Smashed and rusted, it is completely useless now.\n\nHow it got here is hard to say.</VME_AncientStove.description>

<VME_AncientOven.label>ancient oven</VME_AncientOven.label>
<VME_AncientOven.description>An ancient oven. Smashed and rusted, it is completely useless now.\n\nHow it got here is hard to say.</VME_AncientOven.description>

<VME_AncientATM.label>ancient ATM</VME_AncientATM.label>
<VME_AncientATM.description>An ancient ATM. Smashed and rusted, it is completely useless now.\n\nHow it got here is hard to say.</VME_AncientATM.description>

<VME_AncientWashingMachine.label>ancient washing machine</VME_AncientWashingMachine.label>
<VME_AncientWashingMachine.description>An ancient device used for washing textiles. Smashed and rusted, it is completely useless now.\n\nHow it got here is hard to say.</VME_AncientWashingMachine.description>

<VME_AncientHydrant.label>ancient hydrant</VME_AncientHydrant.label>
<VME_AncientHydrant.description>An ancient hydrant. Heavily rusted, it is completely useless now.\n\nHow it got here is hard to say.</VME_AncientHydrant.description>

<VME_AncientMicrowave.label>ancient microwave</VME_AncientMicrowave.label>
<VME_AncientMicrowave.description>An ancient device for heating food. Smashed and rusted, it is completely useless now.\n\nHow it got here is hard to say.</VME_AncientMicrowave.description>

<VME_AncientToilet.label>ancient toilet</VME_AncientToilet.label>
<VME_AncientToilet.description>An ancient toilet. Smashed long ago, it is completely useless now.\n\nHow it got here is hard to say.</VME_AncientToilet.description>

<VME_AncientRefrigerator.label>ancient refrigerator</VME_AncientRefrigerator.label>
<VME_AncientRefrigerator.description>An ancient refrigerator. It was stripped of interesting parts long ago.</VME_AncientRefrigerator.description>

<VME_AncientSmallCrate.label>ancient small crate</VME_AncientSmallCrate.label>
<VME_AncientSmallCrate.description>A small, empty crate which was abandoned ages ago. Its too rusted to store anything.</VME_AncientSmallCrate.description>

<VME_AncientLongCrate.label>ancient long crate</VME_AncientLongCrate.label>
<VME_AncientLongCrate.description>A long, empty crate which was abandoned ages ago. Its too rusted to store anything.</VME_AncientLongCrate.description>

<VME_AncientLargeCrate.label>ancient large crate</VME_AncientLargeCrate.label>
<VME_AncientLargeCrate.description>A large crate which was abandoned ages ago. Its too rusted to store anything.</VME_AncientLargeCrate.description>

<VME_AncientWheel.label>ancient wheel</VME_AncientWheel.label>
<VME_AncientWheel.description>An ancient wheel from some kind of vehicle. The rubber has deteriorated away and the metal is twisted and rusted.</VME_AncientWheel.description>

<VME_AncientGiantWheel.label>ancient giant wheel</VME_AncientGiantWheel.label>
<VME_AncientGiantWheel.description>A giant wheel which came off some large vehicle many ages ago. The rubber has disintegrated away and the metal is twisted and rusted.</VME_AncientGiantWheel.description>

<VME_AncientRustedCar.label>ancient car</VME_AncientRustedCar.label>
<VME_AncientRustedCar.description>An ancient, broken car. Everything that isnt rusted away was looted long ago.</VME_AncientRustedCar.description>

<VME_AncientRustedTruck.label>ancient truck</VME_AncientRustedTruck.label>
<VME_AncientRustedTruck.description>An ancient, broken truck. Everything useful either rusted away or was looted long ago.</VME_AncientRustedTruck.description>

<VME_AncientRustedJeep.label>ancient troop carrier</VME_AncientRustedJeep.label>
<VME_AncientRustedJeep.description>An ancient, broken troop carrier. Everything that isnt rusted away was looted long ago.</VME_AncientRustedJeep.description>

<VME_AncientRustedCarFrame.label>ancient car frame</VME_AncientRustedCarFrame.label>
<VME_AncientRustedCarFrame.description>An ancient, rusted car frame. The body shell has long since rusted away to nothing.</VME_AncientRustedCarFrame.description>

<VME_AncientWarwalkerTorso.label>ancient warwalker torso</VME_AncientWarwalkerTorso.label>
<VME_AncientWarwalkerTorso.description>The torso of a mid-scale warwalker which fell here in ancient days. The valuable parts were looted long ago.</VME_AncientWarwalkerTorso.description>

<VME_AncientRustedDropship.label>ancient dropship</VME_AncientRustedDropship.label>
<VME_AncientRustedDropship.description>The remains of an ancient dropship. The valuable parts were looted long ago and the rest has deteriorated to uselessness.</VME_AncientRustedDropship.description>

<VME_AncientWarwalkerClaw.label>ancient warwalker claw</VME_AncientWarwalkerClaw.label>
<VME_AncientWarwalkerClaw.description>The assault claw of an ancient mid-scale warwalker. This weapon specialized in tearing through heavy plasteel armor at close range. Its valuable components were looted long ago.</VME_AncientWarwalkerClaw.description>

<VME_AncientWarwalkerLeg.label>ancient warwalker leg</VME_AncientWarwalkerLeg.label>
<VME_AncientWarwalkerLeg.description>The shattered leg of a mid-scale warwalker that fell here long ago. It has been picked clean by looters, and no valuable components remain.</VME_AncientWarwalkerLeg.description>

<VME_AncientMiniWarwalkerRemains.label>ancient warsprinter remains</VME_AncientMiniWarwalkerRemains.label>
<VME_AncientMiniWarwalkerRemains.description>The shattered remains of an ancient sub-scale warsprinter. Whatever parts werent ruined when it was destroyed were looted long ago.</VME_AncientMiniWarwalkerRemains.description>

<VME_AncientWarspiderRemains.label>ancient warspider remains</VME_AncientWarspiderRemains.label>
<VME_AncientWarspiderRemains.description>The ruined remains of an ancient mid-scale warspider. It has been picked over many times, and there is nothing valuable left to loot.</VME_AncientWarspiderRemains.description>

<VME_AncientPipelineSection.label>ancient pipeline section</VME_AncientPipelineSection.label>
<VME_AncientPipelineSection.description>A section from an ancient pipeline. It once carried some valuable fluid over long distances. Now its been looted and deteriorated to uselessness.</VME_AncientPipelineSection.description>

<VME_AncientWarwalkerFoot.label>ancient warwalker foot</VME_AncientWarwalkerFoot.label>
<VME_AncientWarwalkerFoot.description>A massive foot from an ancient warwalker. It seems to have been torn free from its owner by some kind of heavy weapon. All the useful components were looted or deteriorated long ago.</VME_AncientWarwalkerFoot.description>

<VME_AncientTank.label>ancient ruined tank</VME_AncientTank.label>
<VME_AncientTank.description>The remains of an ancient tank which was destroyed by some kind of heavy weapon. All the useful components were looted or deteriorated long ago.</VME_AncientTank.description>

<VME_AncientAPC.label>ancient ruined APC</VME_AncientAPC.label>
<VME_AncientAPC.description>The remains of an ancient armoured troop carrier which was destroyed by some kind of heavy weapon. All the useful components were looted or deteriorated long ago.</VME_AncientAPC.description>

<VME_AncientWarwalkerShell.label>ancient warwalker shell</VME_AncientWarwalkerShell.label>
<VME_AncientWarwalkerShell.description>Most of the armored shell of a warwalker. It appears to have been torn off by some colossal weapon system. All the valuable parts were looted, and the rest is badly deteriorated.</VME_AncientWarwalkerShell.description>

<VME_AncientJetEngine.label>ancient jet engine</VME_AncientJetEngine.label>
<VME_AncientJetEngine.description>An ancient jet engine, probably detached from a large airplane. Its delicate internals are rusted to uselessness, and the valuable parts were looted long ago.</VME_AncientJetEngine.description>

<VME_AncientDropshipEngine.label>ancient dropship engine</VME_AncientDropshipEngine.label>
<VME_AncientDropshipEngine.description>An ancient dropship engine. It probably came off a military troop carrier. Its delicate internals are rusted to uselessness, and the valuable parts were looted long ago.</VME_AncientDropshipEngine.description>

<VME_AncientPodCar.label>ancient pod car</VME_AncientPodCar.label>
<VME_AncientPodCar.description>An ancient pod car once capable of automated flight. Its valuable parts were looted long ago, and the rest is badly deteriorated.</VME_AncientPodCar.description>

<VME_AncientTankTrap.label>ancient tank trap</VME_AncientTankTrap.label>
<VME_AncientTankTrap.description>An defensive fortification for stopping vehicles. Its been deteriorating for many years.</VME_AncientTankTrap.description>

<VME_AncientLargeRustedEngineBlock.label>ancient macro-engine block</VME_AncientLargeRustedEngineBlock.label>
<VME_AncientLargeRustedEngineBlock.description>An large, ancient engine block from some giant vehicle or power source. Its rusted through, and all the useful components are gone. No repair could salvage this.</VME_AncientLargeRustedEngineBlock.description>

<VME_AncientFence.label>ancient fence</VME_AncientFence.label>
<VME_AncientFence.description>An ancient fence made of reinforced concrete posts joined by concrete panels.</VME_AncientFence.description>

<VME_AncientRazorWire.label>ancient razor wire</VME_AncientRazorWire.label>
<VME_AncientRazorWire.description>A piece of ancient razor wire. It has been deteriorating for many years and no longer poses any danger.</VME_AncientRazorWire.description>

<VME_AncientPipes.label>ancient pipes</VME_AncientPipes.label>
<VME_AncientPipes.description>A bunch of rusted old pipes. It is hard to say how these ended up here.</VME_AncientPipes.description>

<VME_AncientMegaCannonTripod.label>ancient mega-cannon platform</VME_AncientMegaCannonTripod.label>
<VME_AncientMegaCannonTripod.description>A mounting platform that once held some sort of cannon. It has been broken for many years and every useful component was looted long ago.</VME_AncientMegaCannonTripod.description>

<VME_AncientMegaCannonBarrel.label>ancient mega-cannon barrel</VME_AncientMegaCannonBarrel.label>
<VME_AncientMegaCannonBarrel.description>A barrel from a long-range cannon for artillery or anti-ship use. When it was new, it must have been frighteningly powerful. Now, its far beyond repair and every useful component has been looted.</VME_AncientMegaCannonBarrel.description>

<VME_AncientContainer.label>ancient container</VME_AncientContainer.label>
<VME_AncientContainer.description>A large container from some ancient freight carrying vehicle. It has long since been looted and deteriorted into uselessness.</VME_AncientContainer.description>

<VME_AncientMechanoidShell.label>ancient mechanoid shell</VME_AncientMechanoidShell.label>
<VME_AncientMechanoidShell.description>A shell from a smashed mechanoid. It has been deteriorating for many years and the useful components have disintegrated.</VME_AncientMechanoidShell.description>

<VME_AncientCentipedeShell.label>ancient centipede shell</VME_AncientCentipedeShell.label>
<VME_AncientCentipedeShell.description>A shell from a smashed centipede. It has been deteriorating for many years and all the useful components have disintegrated.</VME_AncientCentipedeShell.description>

<VME_AncientMechDropBeacon.label>ancient mech drop beacon</VME_AncientMechDropBeacon.label>
<VME_AncientMechDropBeacon.description>The broken shell of a mech drop beacon. Its useful components are missing and the shell has deteriorated after many years.</VME_AncientMechDropBeacon.description>

<VME_AncientSecurityTurret.label>ancient security turret</VME_AncientSecurityTurret.label>
<VME_AncientSecurityTurret.description>An ancient, broken security turret. The valuable parts have all been looted or smashed.</VME_AncientSecurityTurret.description>

<VME_AncientRustedEngineBlock.label>ancient engine block</VME_AncientRustedEngineBlock.label>
<VME_AncientRustedEngineBlock.description>An ancient engine block that is rusted through. No repair could salvage this.</VME_AncientRustedEngineBlock.description>

<VME_AncientShipBeacon.label>ancient nav beacon</VME_AncientShipBeacon.label>
<VME_AncientShipBeacon.description>An ancient, broken ship navigation beacon. Every useful component was looted long ago.</VME_AncientShipBeacon.description>

<VME_AncientSpaceJunk.label>ancient space junk</VME_AncientSpaceJunk.label>
<VME_AncientSpaceJunk.description>Ancient chunks of space junk that fell from orbit. Perhaps a relic of an ancient space battle.</VME_AncientSpaceJunk.description>


		<!-- +++++ Buildings_Ideo +++++ -->
<VME_WickerMan.label>wicker man</VME_WickerMan.label>
<VME_WickerMan.description>A large humanoid figure made out of dry brush, thatch, and wood scraps. Prisoners have to be physically restrained to the figurine then burned alive as part of a trial or ritual.</VME_WickerMan.description>

<VME_Bonfire.label>bonfire</VME_Bonfire.label>
<VME_Bonfire.description>An incredibly large and bright-burning bonfire made out of a carefully organized pile of logs on a stone base. Used heavily during flame-based rituals and can only be placed outdoors.</VME_Bonfire.description>
<VME_BonfireAfterRitual.label>bonfire</VME_BonfireAfterRitual.label>
<VME_BonfireAfterRitual.description>An incredibly large and bright-burning bonfire made out of a carefully organized pile of logs on a stone base. Used heavily during flame-based rituals and can only be placed outdoors. Will last for at least two quadrums and provide beauty nearby, as well as count for the Fire: Desired precept.</VME_BonfireAfterRitual.description>

<VME_MechanoidEffigy.label>mechanoid effigy</VME_MechanoidEffigy.label>
<VME_MechanoidEffigy.description>A structure assembled from scrapped mechanoid parts. Emits an IFF programming signal capable of confusing ancient mechanoid receptors. Should two exist per colonist enough signal noise will soft reset ancient mechanoid programming, causing an immediate retreat.</VME_MechanoidEffigy.description>

<VME_Obelisk.label>ominous obelisk</VME_Obelisk.label>
<VME_Obelisk.description>An ominous-looking obelisk of pure chiseled stone. It seems to radiate an aura of hopelessness and despair.\n\nThe Corruption need of any colonist in an obelisks radius of effect wont decrease.</VME_Obelisk.description>

<VME_InsectNest.label>insect nest</VME_InsectNest.label>
<VME_InsectNest.description>A large, swollen hive that seems to be seeping high amounts of bubbling insectoid jelly but not incubating any insectoids themselves.\n\nThe nest will need maintenance by a colonist with the insectoid herder role. If maintenance reaches 0%, the nest will be destroyed.</VME_InsectNest.description>


</LanguageData>